l love his eidetic memory. It's so sexy.
(Amy:)Sheldon, what are the ingredients
in Pringles?
(Sheldon:)Dried potatoes vegetable oil,
corn flour, wheat starch...
...maItodextrin, saIt,
and my favorite ingredient of all...
(Sheldon:)...uniformity.
(Amy:)The uterus quivers, does it not?
(Leonard:)There's Howard's rocket...
(Leonard:)- ...live from Kazakhstan.
- Oh, I'm so nervous.
(Bernadette:)I don't think I can watch.
(Raj:)You're nervous? I've been stress-eating
for four days. Look at me.
(Raj:)I'm wearing my fat pants.
(Sheldon:)Remarkable.
ln just under a haIf hour,
200 metric tons of fuel will ignite...
(Sheldon:)...in a controlled explosion
right beneath Howard's keister.
(Sheldon:)And all from a country whose entire
contribution to the global economy...
...has been "Tetris"
and mail-order brides.
(Bernadette:)Give me those damn Pringles.
(Howard:)MAN
(Mike:)Okay, we're in the final countdown.
(Mike:)- How you doing over there?
- Good, good.
(Howard:)Quick question.
I missed it in the briefing.
(Howard:)How much urine do these suits hold?